<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>HALO: Rimworld Auxiliary Combat Armory (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.HALORimworldAuxiliaryCombatArmory</packageId>
  <author>Helixien</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/HALORimworldAuxiliaryCombatArmory</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Helixiens mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1961456342
with permission

[b]The release of RimWorld 1.6 added improved support for [url=https://github.com/emipa606/AssetBuilder/blob/main/README.md]Asset Bundles[/url][/b].
To avoid doubling the size of the mod, it was re-released using only Asset Bundles, you can find the previous version of this mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3435308436]here[/url].

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/HALORimworldAuxiliaryCombatArmory][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/gUqRJQq.png[/img]

Hello everyone!
With the MCC finally being on Steam and me playing Halo Reach a lot, I had the urge to add some weapons of the Halo Universe to Rimworld, but in a vanilla-friendly way (like Oskar Potocki does it).

"Halo: Rimworld Auxiliary Combat Armory" (HRACA) is a simple weapons mod, aiming to add some of the most beloved UNSC weapons from Halo to Rimworld in a vanilla-friendly way. Unlike most people who just add a weapon 1:1 from the game it is from, I aim to modify them so they fit into the world of Rimworld and its lore. To achieve this I have heavily changed their designs, as well as made all of them charge weapons. Do not worry, they still have their classic sounds we all know and love.

Nearly all of them can be crafted (assuming you have done the required research and got a pawn in your colony with the required crafting skill), found on random pawns or be bought from traders. All of them have been tweaked as best I can so they are neither overpowered, not underpowered and can compete with vanilla charge guns, as well as guns added by other mods.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/rpsUpYG.png[/img]

"HALO: Rimworld Auxiliary Combat Armory" (HRACA) comes with following weapons.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/YaLWFCq.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/hwbsnnZ.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/bP9b4pQ.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/kDkEI5W.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/mv2l4V7.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Arbz20F.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/yFGtOFK.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NCs3tC6.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Q1uWfMd.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/I0o8dOO.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/HSkN5Oq.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/rJdnbrx.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Dqi5p64.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/ous7C6y.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/fKtSZMF.png[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/6KijhOH.png[/img]

Q: Do HRACA weapons spawn on enemies and friendlies?
A: Yes, they are integrated into the vanilla weapons list.

Q: Is it Combat Extended compatible?
A: To my knowledge a patch is being provided by CE.

Q: Why should I use this mod over any other Halo mod on the workshop?
A: These weapons are made for people who want their custom content to perfectly fit the vanilla game. No other Halo mod offers that. This is just how I would add them.

Q: How do I get the classic Halo sounds for the weapons?
A: Download the patch and load it right after this mod.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/UOstAlO.png[/img]

The concepts of these weapons are property of Bungie/343i. I do not claim these as my own!

Graphics are made by me, inspired by Halo weapons.

Special thanks to Oskar Potocki for his mentoring and help.
Also thank you Chowder for giving me the idea for the name.

Rimworld is owned by Tynan Sylvester.

[url=https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/]CC BY-NC-ND 4.0[/url] (applies only to graphics)

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]  | tags:  halo,  unsc</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.6.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>